Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ganesh-shinde-2906 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Amazon Web Services (AWS) Red Hat Linux DevSecOps

Certifications

AWS Solution Architect

Ganesh Shinde

Cloud And DevOps Engineer at Ugam Thane

Summary

Over 4+ years of progressive experience in the field of Information Technology which include skills for setting up and giving Solutions to Big Data, Aws and Linux, Windows Infrastructure.

Certifications:-AWS Solution Architecture

Technical Skills:-

Linux Server Administration

Windows Server Administration

Apache/CDH/HDP Hadoop Cluster Administration

Storm Cluster Administration

AWS Administration/Designing/Solution Provider

Apache/Ngnix/Tomcat Administration

DB Administrator:- MySQL, InfluxDB, PostGreSQL, SQL.

DevOps:-Jenkins CI/CD, Ansible, Docker, Kubernates, Terraform.

Load Testing:- Apache Jmeter.

Shell Scripting:- Python, YAML

Experience

Ugam

Cloud And DevOps Engineer

June 2021 - Present (9 months)

India

Siemens Technology India Cloud Architect May 2020 - June 2021 (1 year 2 months) Navi Mumbai, Maharashtra

Medicalwale.com AWS Admin August 2018 - May 2020 (1 year 10 months)

Page 1 of 2

Ecospace I.T Park, Andheri -(E)

Managing AWS production infrastructure on EC2 and S3.Launching EC2instances. Creating different backups scripts as per week/monthly/dalily requirement and sharing it at different locations like S3,SAN etc. Working on IAM user management to provide single bucket access using custom policy. Mointoring User activity and configuration changes done on AWS Account using Config and Cloudtrail service. Done production setup of CDN using CloudFront-web, also enabled advanced features on URI using apache and ELB.

Setting Up Data Analytics Tools like Mammoth, Google Data Studio, Quick Sight and Tableau .

CloudAied I.T Solutions
Jr.Linux Engineer
February 2018 - August 2018 (7 months)
Ashar Estate, Wagle Estate, Thane -W

Setting up Nagios And Monitoring AWS Servers.

Education

anand vishwa gurukul senior night college Bachelor of Science in Information Technology, B.Sc.I.T · (2014 - 2017)